Guide to the Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Undergraduate affairs, Yale College, records of the dean
1955-2011
RU 95
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
37.08
(53 boxes)
The records consist of subject files maintained by the deans of Undergraduate Affairs and Student Affairs of Yale College, concerning the administration of undergraduate student life, student organizations, orientation programs, athletics, and student housing.
Yale College (1887- ). Dean's Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-B (YRG 9-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant deans of Yale College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files maintained by the dean of Undergraduate Affairs and Student Affairs of Yale College, concerning the administration of undergraduate student life, student organizations, orientation programs, athletics, and student housing.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Deans (Education); Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale College (1887- ). Administration; Yale College (1887- ). Dean's Office; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Student housing; Yale University -- Students
- Records of Marnesba Hill as Dean of Student Affairs, 1962-1978; Accession 1976-A-007
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 2 folders 26-30 restricted until January 1, 2054.
  - A Better Chance, Incorporated (ABC), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Activities fee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Assistant job, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Admissions Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Admissions
    - Ratio, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Transfer program, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 13)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 14 - 15)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Afro-Board Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Application for change of college affiliation: forms, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Asian Americans, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Athletics: women's, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Berkeley College, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Black Administrators, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Black American Law Students Association (BALSA), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Black Environmental Studies Team (BEST), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Black faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Black graduate students, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Black students, 1952-1974 (Box 2, Folder 28 - 29)
  - Black students at Yale (BSAY), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Board scores, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Boggs Academy, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Branford College, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Calendar
    - Academic, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Yale College, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Calhoun College, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Campus' police, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Career Advisory Service, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Career Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Chairman and Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1974
    - Postgraduation plans (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Low testers (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Classroom events, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Co-education, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Co-education, Committee on, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - College Council, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Concerns, Commit tee for, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Connecticut College, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence
    - 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 49 - 54)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 55 - 56)
  - Council of Masters, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 57 - 58)
  - Consumer Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Course changes for fall term, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Davenport College (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Daytop, Inc.
    - 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Debate Squad, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Discretionary Fund: College Deans, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - The Drum (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Timothy Dwight College (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - The Education of Women, Committee on, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 69 - 70)
  - Jonathan Edwards College (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Faculty advisors, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Faculty Advisory Commit tee, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Faculty meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Fellowships, Yale College, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Fellowships, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Financial Aid, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Freshman Dean's gift, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Freshman loan account, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - General Honors: statistics, 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Grades, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Higher Education Committee (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Honors and Special Projects Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 84 - 85)
  - Housekeeping and Physical Plant Services (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Housing
    - Annexes, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Off-campus, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 88 - 92)
    - Requests to live off-campus second term, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - International Health, Committee on, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Meetings of College Deans, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 96 - 97)
  - Minority Teacher Recruitment Program, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Morse College (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Parent's Day, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Pierson College (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Plagiarism, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Police records, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Police reports, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Posters, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Premedical Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Prizes (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Pre-registration Orientation Program
    - 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - 1974 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - 1974 Aug 14 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Budget, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Budget, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Program faculty, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Student evaluation (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Puerto Rican students (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Readmissions, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 118 - 119)
  - Recommendations: statements of Dean of Students (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Requests for checks, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Saybrook College (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Scholarships (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Scholarships and loans, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Senior Class Council, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - SHE: Information for Women at Yale, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Silliman College, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Stiles, Ezra College, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Student census, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Student employees, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Student employment, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Student organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Student parking, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Student records, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Summer Academic Programs Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 135 - 136)
  - Summer Programs
    - Answers for minority students, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Applications and budgets, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 138 - 139)
    - Cancelled, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Summer Programs Conferences Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Summer Study: proposals for, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 142 - 143)
  - Summer Term, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Symphony Orchestra (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Teacher preparation, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Teaching and Learning, Committee on, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Transfer students, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Trumbull College, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Agency: accounts, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Undergraduate regulations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Upward Bound (Box 10, Folder 152)
- Records of Marnesba Hill and others as Dean of Student Affairs, 1963-1981; Accession 1984-A-031
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017.
  - Admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1974 - Women, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1975
    - List by Campus Address, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - List by Colleges, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1976, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Coeducation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - College Seminars - Committee on Teaching - Employment Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Summer Program, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Deans' Meetings
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Office
    - Yale College, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Yale College - Procedures, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Department Mailing Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Film Making, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Financial Aid - Student Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Financial Records
    - Acting Instructors - Employment Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Budget Maintenance, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Career Advisory, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - 1968-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Five Year B.A. Program, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Freshman Counselees, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Freshman Counselor Files
    - Applicants
      - 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Budget File, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Calendar, Bulletin, Regulations, Schedule, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Cancelled, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Class of 1979, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - College and Rooming Association, Freshmen, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence (after being accepted as Freshman Counselor), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Counselors
      - 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - A-Z
        - 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 38 - 40)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 41 - 43)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 44 - 47)
      - A-L, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - M-Z, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 49 - 50)
      - A-Z, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 51 - 53)
      - Black, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Expense Records, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Faculty Talks: Class of 1979, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Faculty Program Advisors: Class of 1979, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Housing, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 58 - 59)
    - Information, correspondence, memoranda, lists, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 60 - 61)
    - Information, general, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 62 - 66)
    - Inquiries, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 67 - 68)
    - Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Meals, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Mailings: Class of 1979, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Memorandas (extra copies\), 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Miscellaneous: correspondence, memoranda, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Orientation, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Orientation and Registration, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Orientation and Training, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Orientation and Training Session, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Originals, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Preparation for Counselors Return (mid-year), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Program, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 80 - 81)
    - Reallocation: Class of 1979, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Recruiting Material
      - 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 83)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Rejections A-Z
      - 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 85 - 86)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 87 - 88)
    - Reserves
      - 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Sample Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Withdrawals, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Withdrawals: Floating Freshman Counselors, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Withdrawn, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Freshman Reallocation, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Junior Year Abroad, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Law School Admissions - Minority Students, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Medicine, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Minority Opportunities (including women), 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Minority Retention, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Minority Students, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Minority Students - Financial Aid, undated (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Moore Fund Proposals, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Pre-Law, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - PROP (Pre-registration Orientation Program), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Projects, Special, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Teaching Fellows, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Texaco Questionnaire, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Tutoring
    - 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Tutorial Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Information, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Students Requesting Tutoring over Reading Period, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Tutors
    - 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Administrative Science and Statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Biology, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Chemistry, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Economics, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - History, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Languages, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Mathematics, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Philosophy, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Physics (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Undergraduate Financial Aid: Gift and Loan Funds - Basic Packet, undated (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Undergraduate Housing
    - 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 129 - 130)
    - Annex Housing, memo replies, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Freshmen, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Residential Colleges, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Room Fines, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Saybrook Housing Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Undergraduate Organizations
    - 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 136 - 137)
    - Activities Registration, undated (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Agendas, minutes, registration, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Alpha Phi Omega, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - AISEC, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Asian-American Students Association, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - American Association for Higher Education (A.A.H.E.), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Associated Student Agencies, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Baker's Dozen, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Bridge Club, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Black Community, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Budgets, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Career Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Chess Club, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Committee on Status of Minority Students., 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Committees on Undergraduate Organizations
      - 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 152)
      - Minutes, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 153)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 154)
      - Meetings
        - 1977 Oct 13 (Box 10, Folder 155)
        - 1977 Oct 20 (Box 10, Folder 156)
        - 1977 Nov 18 (Box 10, Folder 157)
        - 1977 Dec 12 (Box 10, Folder 158)
        - 1978 Oct 9 (Box 10, Folder 159)
        - 1978 Oct 17 (Box 10, Folder 160)
        - 1978 Oct 31 (Box 10, Folder 161)
        - 1978 Dec 5 (Box 10, Folder 162)
        - 1978 Feb 3 (Box 10, Folder 163)
        - 1978 Apr 4 (Box 10, Folder 164)
        - 1979 Feb 20 (Box 10, Folder 165)
        - 1979 Apr 11 (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - Committee to Review Policies and Procedures for Undergraduate Organizations, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - Coordination and Eligibility Committee
      - Eligibility Cases, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 168)
      - Policy, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - Coordination and Eligibility Requirements - Minutes/ Related Committees, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Council on Global Affairs, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Council on Third World Women, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Debate, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - DKE, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Dramatic Association, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Fraternities and Sororities, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Funds Administration, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Insurance, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 179 - 180)
    - International Student Center, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 181)
    - Liberal Party, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 182)
    - Mexican-American Students, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 183)
    - Minority Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 184)
    - Minority Advisory Council, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 185)
    - Minority Students, Committee to Review the Status of in Yale College, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 186)
    - Minority Women's Forum, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 187)
    - Minutes, agendas, lists, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 188)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 189)
    - Miscellaneous Studies concerning Undergraduates, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 190)
    - N.C.A.A. Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 191)
    - New Journal, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 192)
    - News, Yale Daily, 1949-1972 (Box 12, Folder 193)
    - OFF Film Society, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 194)
    - Phelps Association
      - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 195)
      - Basic Packet (Box 12, Folder 196)
    - Political Union, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 197)
    - Puerto Rican Students, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 198)
    - Recycling, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - Rental Fees, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Report of the Committee to Review Policies and Procedures for Undergraduate Organizations, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 201)
    - Requests for Space, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 202)
    - Shockley-Rusher Debate, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 203)
    - Space Allocations, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 204 - 206)
    - Student Agencies, 1973-1972 (Box 13, Folder 207 - 208)
    - Student Advisory Board, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 209)
    - Student Entertainment Committee, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 210)
    - Students' International Mediational Society (S.I.M.S.), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 211)
    - Student Organizations, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 212)
    - Student Organizations List, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 213)
    - Third World Organizations, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 214)
    - Urban Improvement Corps, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 215)
    - Undergraduate Affairs
      - 1955-1964 (Box 14, Folder 216)
      - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 217)
      - Office, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 218)
    - Undergraduate Representatives on University Committees, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 219)
    - Women's Caucus, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 220 - 221)
    - Women's Legislative Action, Committee on, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 222)
    - WYBC, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 223)
    - Yale College Council - Survival Guide, undated (Box 14, Folder 224)
    - Yale Seal/ Yale Name, Requests for Use of, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 225)
  - Undergraduate Regulations, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 226 - 227)
  - RESTRICTED
    - Academic problems, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 228)
    - Financial Records - Personnel Forms, 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 229 - 233)
    - Freshman Counselor Files
      - Mid-Year Report, Counselors, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 234)
      - Salaries, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 235 - 237)
    - Undergraduate Financial Aid (Box 16, Folder 238)
    - Gifts and Loans Fund - Yale College Dean's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 239)
    - Gift Requests, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 240)
    - Long Term Loans, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 241)
    - Scholarships, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 242)
    - Short Term Loans, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 243)
    - Student Loans, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 244)
    - Undergraduate Organizations: The Yale Political (Magazine), 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 245 - 246)
- Records of the Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, 1956-1987; Accession 1989-A-029
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023.
  - Yale Student Groups
    - American Field Service (AFS): In-House Archives, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Apartheid Coalition at Yale, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - In-House Archives
      - Asian-American Student Alliance (USA), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Aurelian Honor Society, 1957-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Black Students: Black Students' Alliance (BSAY), 1972-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Casa Cultural Julia De Burgos, [1977]-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Clan Na Gael Publicity, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Despierta Boricua, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Freshman Outdoor Orientation Trips Publicity, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Gay Students' Center, 1973-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Liberal Party of the Political Union, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - MEChA, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Walden: Student-to-Student Counseling, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Yale Amateur Radio Society, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - The Party of the Right, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Yale Charities Drive, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Yale Debate Association
        - Finances, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Accounting Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Expense Reports--Check Requests, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Finances, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Expenses, etc., 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Check Requests, etc., 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Personnel, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Yale Business and Economic Forum, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Yale College Council
        - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Archive, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Yale Chess Club, 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Yale Christian Fellowship, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Yale College Republicans, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Yale Dancers, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Yale Guild of Carillonneur, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Yale Hunger Action Project, 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Yale International Relations, Inc. (Model U.N.), 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Yale Political Union, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Yale Outing Club, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Yale Political Union
        - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - AISEC (International Association of Students in Economics and Management), 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Yale Recycling, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Yale Russian Chorus, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Yale Slavic Chorus, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Yale Student Chapter of Amnesty International, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Yale Undergraduate Women's Caucus, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Yale University Dramatic Association
        - 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
        - Check Requests and Contracts, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
        - Accounting Statements, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)